let questions = [
    {
        question: 'Oslo',
        options: [
            'Kuwait',
            'Norway',
            'Uruguay',
            'Montenegro'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Havana',
        options: [
            'New Zealand',
            'Bolivia',
            'Cuba',
            'Rwanda'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Dili',
        options: [
            'Qatar',
            'Latvia',
            'Iceland',
            'East Timor'
        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Skopje',
        options: [
            'Taiwan (Republic of China)',
            'North Macedonia',
            'Tanzania',
            'Thailand'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Madrid',
        options: [
            'Comoros',
            'Liberia',
            'Yemen',
            'Spain'
        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Bangkok',
        options: [
            'Bahrain',
            'Greece',
            'North Korea',
            'Thailand'
        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Paramaribo',
        options: [
            'Suriname',
            'Honduras',
            'Cambodia',
            'The Bahamas'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Bandar Seri Begawan',
        options: [
            'Netherlands',
            'Brunei',
            'Angola',
            'Ireland'
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Beirut',
        options: [
            'United Kingdom',
            'Portugal',
            'Lebanon',
            'Guatemala'
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Saint Johns',
        options: [
            'Nauru',
            'South Sudan',
            'Antigua and Barbuda',
            'Comoros'
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Do you like the quiz?',
        options: [
            'Sim',
            'NÃ£o',
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
];